A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), B-0230, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 905)
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), B-0375, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 906)
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), The Visionaries, DF-0312, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 907)
  - ISAR (Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia), B-0474, 2004-2006 (Box 83, Folder 908)
  - Ithaca College, B-0662, 2005-2008 (Box 83, Folder 909-910)
  - Ithaca College, B-0662, Now Is the Winter, Moscow Project Images, Exhibition Reviews (Box 83, Folder 909)
  - Ithaca College, B-0662, Now Is the Winter, Ithaca Symposium Images, Nicholas Muellner (Box 83, Folder 909)
  - Ivy Baldwin Dance, DF-0819, 2000-2001, 2003-2004, 2006-2009 (Box 83, Folder 911)
  - Ivy Baldwin Dance, DF-0819, Ivy Baldwin Dance, Romania (Box 83, Folder 911)
  - Ivy Baldwin Dance, DF-0819, It's Only Me, Ivy Baldwin Dance (Box 83, Folder 911)
  - Ivy Baldwin Dance, DF-0819, Could Be Nice, Ivy Baldwin Dance (Box 83, Folder 911)
  - Jacob's Pillow Dance, EC-0310, 2002-2003, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 912)
  - Jacob's Pillow Dance, EC-0310, Irma Omerzo'a "Mi-Nous" Performed by Nikolina Bujas-Pristas and Pravsan Delahovic in Doris Duke's Studio Theatre, 2003 August (Box 83, Folder 912)
  - Jacob's Pillow, B-0663, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 913)
  - Jacob's Pillow, B-0663, Jacob's Pillow, Moving Dace for 75 Years, 75th Anniversary Season, Overview DVD (Box 83, Folder 913)
  - Jazz at Lincoln Center, DF-0412, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 914)
  - Jazz at Lincoln Center, Miscellaneous, DF-0412, 1998-2000, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 915)
  - Jewish Community Development, DF-0413, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 84, Folder 916)
  - The Jewish Museum, DF-0139, DF-0331, 2001-2004, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 917)
  - The Jewish Museum, DF-0340, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 918)
  - The Jewish Museum, Miscellaneous, DF-0340, 2006-2007 (Box 84, Folder 919)
  - The Jewish Museum, DF-0611, 2006-2009 (Box 84, Folder 920)
  - The Jewish Museum, DF-0806, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 921)
  - John Jasperse Company, B-0320, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 84, Folder 922)
  - John Jasperse Company, DF-0623, 2005-2006 (Box 84, Folder 923)
  - John Kelly & Company, DF-0422, 2004, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 924)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0219, B-0300, B-0400, 1996-2000, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 925)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, Miscellaneous, B-0219, 2000, 2004, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 926)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0607, B-0700, 2005-2009 (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0602, B-0700, Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, Supplementary Materials, Dmitri Tsvetkov (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0602, B-0700, Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, Supplementary Materials, Georgy Litichevsky, 2005-2008 (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0602, B-0700, Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, Supplementary Materials, Vadim Zakharov "No Distance" Exhibition, 2005-2008 (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0602, B-0700, Joseph Brodsky Fund, V. Zakhrov (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joseph Brodsky Memorial Fellowship, B-0513, B-0602, B-0700, 2006 Brodsky Fellow - D. Tsvetkov (Box 84, Folder 927)
  - Joslyn Art Museum, B-0360, 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 928)
  - Julia Ritter Performance Group, DF-0315, 2001-2004 (Box 85, Folder 929)
  - Julia Ritter Performance Group, DF-0517, 2003-2007 (Box 85, Folder 930)
  - Julia Ritter Performance Group, DF-0517, Julia Ritter Performance Group, Dragan Dragin, Prague Project, Photos, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 930)
  - Jump Start Performance, Miscellaneous, B-0866, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 931)
  - Kadmus Theater Studio, B-0151, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 85, Folder 932)
  - Kadmus Theater Studio, B-0418, 2004, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 933)
  - Keep the Country Dancing, B-0197, 1993-1994, 2001-2002 (Box 85, Folder 934)
  - Kennedy Center, B-0205, 2001-2003 (Box 85, Folder 935)
  - The Kitchen, B-0250, 1999-2003, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 936)
  - The Kitchen, DF-0518, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 937)
  - Kitka, B-0477, 1999, 2001-2002, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 938)
  - Kitka, B-0821, 2007-2010 (Box 86, Folder 939)
  - Kitka, Miscellaneous, B-0821 (Box 86, Folder 940)
  - Kronos Quartet, EC-0412, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 941)
  - Kronos Quartet, Miscellaneous, EC-0412, 2000, 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 942)
  - Kronos Quartet, B-0558, 2002-2006 (Box 86, Folder 943)
  - La Jolla Playhouse, DF-0414, 2004-2007 (Box 86, Folder 944)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., B-0172, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 945)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0108, 2000-2001, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 946)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., "Indifference", DF-0114, 2000-2001, 2003, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 947)
  - La Mama E.T.C., EC-0400, 2002-2205 (Box 87, Folder 948)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0526, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 949)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0600, 2005-2007 (Box 87, Folder 950)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, DF-0600, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 951)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, DF-0600, Aesclepius Project at Academy of Tirana, Albania, Report from Albania, 2006 March 28-April 10 (Box 87, Folder 951)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, DF-0600, La MaMa ETC., The Raven, Venice Biennale 2006, 2006 July (Box 87, Folder 951)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, DF-0600, La MaMa ETC., The Raven (Excerpts) by Ellen Stewart, Venice Biennale 2006, 2006 July (Box 87, Folder 951)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0609, 2005-2007 (Box 87, Folder 952)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0629, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 953)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., "Brothers", B-0723, DF-0813, 2006-2009 (Box 87, Folder 954)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., "Gardzienice", B-0724, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 955)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., EC-0702, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 956)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, EC-0702, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 957)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, EC-0702, Preview and Review, Production Photos of "Diana" at National Theatre of Kosovo, 2007 July 7-8 (Box 87, Folder 957)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., Miscellaneous, EC-0702, La MaMa Archive, Diana, National Theater of Kosovo, 2007 July 7 (Box 87, Folder 957)
  - La MaMa E.T.C., DF-0808, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 958)
  - La Pocha Nostra, DF-0227, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 959)
  - The Lab, Sue Mark, DF-0228, 2002-2004 (Box 87, Folder 960)
  - The Lab, Sue Mark, DF-0228, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 960)
  - Laboratory for International Theatre Exchange, DF-0213, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 961)
  - LakeNet, B-0172, 2001-2005 (Box 87, Folder 962)
  - LakeNet, Miscellaneous, B-0172, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 963)
  - Lampo, DF-0624, 2005-2007 (Box 88, Folder 964)
  - Lampo, DF-0624, Lampo, "Sound Exchange" Photos (Box 88, Folder 964)
  - Lampo, DF-0624, Lampo, "Sound Exchange", ANS Sound Recording (Box 88, Folder 964)
  - Lark Play Development Center, DF-0737, 2006-2008 (Box 88, Folder 965)
  - Lark Play Development Center, B-0822, 2006-2010 (Box 88, Folder 966)
  - Lark Play Development Center, B-0822, Lark Play Development Center, Trip to Romania for American-Romanian Theatre Exchange, 2010 May (Box 88, Folder 966)
  - Lark Play Development Center, B-0822, Lark, U.S.-Romanian Exchange Photos, 2008-2009 (Box 88, Folder 966)
  - Leah Stein Dance Company, B-0361, 1997, 1999, 2001-2007 (Box 88, Folder 967)
  - Leah Stein Dance Company, B-0361, LSDC, Poland, Romania (Box 88, Folder 967)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0206, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 968)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0362, 2003-2004 (Box 88, Folder 969)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0362, Lincoln Center Festival 2004, Selects, Forbidden Xmass/Doctor & Patient, Pyotr Fomenko-Egyptian Nights, Pyotr Fomenko-War & Peace, Stephanie Burger-Photography Inc. (Box 88, Folder 969)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0761, 2007-2009 (Box 88, Folder 970)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0761, Peasant Opera, Bela Pinter Theatre (Box 88, Folder 970)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0761, "Liliom", Kretakor Theatre (Box 88, Folder 970)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0761, The Seagull, Kretakor Theatre (Disk 1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 970)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, B-0761, The Seagull, Kretakor Theatre (Disk 2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 970)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, EC-0703, 2006-2008 (Box 88, Folder 971)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Digital Images: Programs from Mongolia, Lincoln Center Festival 2007 (Box 88, Folder 971)
  - Link Vostok, B-0198, 2001-2003 (Box 88, Folder 972)
  - Link Vostok, B-0321, 2002-2004 (Box 89, Folder 973)
  - Link Vostok, B-0363, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 974)
  - Link Vostok, B-0461, 2003-2006 (Box 89, Folder 975)
  - Link Vostok, B-0559, 2005-2007 (Box 89, Folder 976)
  - Link Vostok, B-0762, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 977)
  - Link Vostok, B-0762, Art of Movement 2006 Link Vostok (Box 89, Folder 977)
  - Links Hall, B-0823, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 978)
  - Links Hall, Miscellaneous, B-0823, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 979)
  - Liss Fain Dance, B-0725, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 980)
  - Livingston Ripley Waterfowl Sanctuary, DF-0525, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 981)
  - Location One, B-0199, 2001-2003 (Box 89, Folder 982)
  - Location One: B-0199, Dominik Lejman, Images of Artists work (Box 89, Folder 982)
  - Location One B-0199, Dominik Lejman, Images of Artists work (Box 89, Folder 982)
  - Location One, Miscellaneous, B-0199, 1998-2001 (Box 90, Folder 983)
  - Location One, Go home Project 2001-2002, DF-0127, 2000-2002, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 984)
  - Location One, DF-0328, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 984)
  - Location One, Miscellaneous, DF-0328, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 985)
  - Location One, B-0491, 2000-2005 (Box 90, Folder 986)
  - Location One, B-0491, Marlena Kudicka, Work, 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 986)
  - Location One, DF-0601, 2005-2007 (Box 90, Folder 987)
  - Location One, Miscellaneous, DF-0601, 2003, 2005, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 988)
  - Location One, B-0763, 2007-2009 (Box 90, Folder 989)
  - Location One, B-0763, Location One International Residency Program, Nicolas Grospierre, Poland (Box 90, Folder 989)
  - Long Beach Opera, B-0209, 2001-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 90, Folder 990)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, B-01112, 1997-1998, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 90, Folder 991)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, B-0220, 2001-2007 (Box 90, Folder 992)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic, B-0420, 2003-2006 (Box 91, Folder 993)
  - Lower East Side Printshop, B-0221, 2001-2004 (Box 91, Folder 994)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, B-0251, 2002-2003 (Box 91, Folder 995)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, EC-0607, 2005-2007 (Box 91, Folder 996)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, Miscellaneous, EC-0607, 2004-2005 (Box 91, Folder 997)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, B-0514, 2004-2006 (Box 91, Folder 998)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, DF-0632, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 999)
  - Lumina String Quartet, DF-0437, 1993, 1996, 1999-2005, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 1000)
  - Ma-Yi Theatre Company, B-0764, 2007-2009 (Box 91, Folder 1001)
  - Ma-Yi Theatre Company, B-0764, Ma-Yi's Theatre Company's The Romance of Magno Rubio, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 1001)
  - Mabou Mines, Animal Magnetism, B-0513, 2001-2003 (Box 91, Folder 1002)
  - Mabou Mines, DF-0320, 2003, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 1003)
  - Mabou Mines, DF-0329, 2003, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 1004)
  - Mabou Mines, B-0726, 2006-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1005)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, B-0288, 2000-2003 (Box 92, Folder 1006)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, DF-0415, 2001, 2003-2006 (Box 92, Folder 1007)
  - Maida Withers Dance Consruction Company, B-0515, 2001, 2004-2007 (Box 92, Folder 1008)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, B-0624, 2001, 2005-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1009)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, B-0624, Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, Thresholds Crossed (Box 92, Folder 1009)
  - Mannes College of Music, DF-0604, 2005-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1010)
  - Mannes College of Music, DF-0648, 2004-2008 (Box 93, Folder 1011)
  - The Mapleton Community Foundation, B-0533, 2004-2008 (Box 93, Folder 1012)
  - The Mapleton Community Foundation, B-0533, Mapleton Community Foundation, Siuslaw/Sakhalin, Carolyn Knox, 2007 February (Box 93, Folder 1012)
  - The Mapleton Community Foundation, B-0778, 2007-2008 (Box 93, Folder 1013)
  - Marcel Marceau Foundation for the Advancement of the Art of Mime, DF-0508, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 1014)
  - Mary Ellen Childs' Crash, DF-0307, 2002-2003 (Box 93, Folder 1015)
  - Maryland Institute College of Art, B-0514, 2000-2001, 2003, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 1016)
  - Meredith Monk, The House Foundation, B-0089, 1999-2001 (Box 93, Folder 1017)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0289, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 1018)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, DF-0208, 2001-2003 (Box 93, Folder 1019)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0421, 2003-2005 (Box 93, Folder 1020)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0462, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 1021)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Miscellaneous, B-0462, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 1022)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0516, 2004-2006, 2008-2009 (Box 93, Folder 1023)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Met/Kremlin Exchange 2006, B-0560, 2000, 2005-2007 (Box 93, Folder 1024)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0625, 2000, 2006-2009 (Box 93, Folder 1025)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Met/Kremlin, B-0664, 2000, 2006-2008 (Box 93, Folder 1026)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Florica Zaharia to Romania, DF-0606, 2005-2006 (Box 94, Folder 1027)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Florica Zaharia to Romania, Miscellaneous, DF-0606 (Box 94, Folder 1028)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, EC-0612, 2006-2007 (Box 94, Folder 1026)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Miscellaneous, EC-0612, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 1030)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Hermitage Museum Exchange, B-0727, 2000, 2006-2008 (Box 94, Folder 1031)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Romanian Exchange Program, B-0728, 2006-2008 (Box 94, Folder 1032)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Romanian Exchange Program, Miscellaneous, B-0728, 2007 (Box 94, Folder 1033)
  - Cuceuteni Culture, 2015:015:054
  - The Bucovina's Village Museum, 2015:015:055
  - Como rile Tricolor Thracian Treasures, 2015:015:056
  - Bucovina, 2015:015:057
  - Bucovina: Tourist Guide, 2015:015:058
  - Archeological Treasures Restored in Bucovina, 2015:015:059
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Kremlin Exchange, B-0765, 2000, 2006-2009 (Box 94, Folder 1034)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Hermitage Exchange, B-0824, 2000, 2007-2008 (Box 94, Folder 1035)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Romanian Exchange Program, B-0825, 2000, 2007-2009 (Box 94, Folder 1036)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, B-0867, 2008-2009 (Box 94, Folder 1037)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation, EC-0704, 2007-2008 (Box 95, Folder 1038)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation, EC-0804, EC-0900, 2007-2011 (Box 95, Folder 1040)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation, Miscellaneous, EC-0804, EC-0900, 2007-2008 (Box 95, Folder 1040)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation: Ujazdowski Castle, B-0826, 2007-2010 (Box 95, Folder 1041)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation: Ujazdowski Castle, B-0826, CSW, Monika Weiss, SUSTENAZO (Box 95, Folder 1041)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation: Ujazdowski Castle, B-0826, Monika Weiss, wywid Polskie Radio, wywiad Qadrans Qltuy, SUSTENAZO (Box 95, Folder 1041)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation Workshop, Ujazdowski Castle, Miscellaneous, B-0826, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 1042)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, DF-0602, 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 1043)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, DF-0602, FAMU Photos (Box 95, Folder 1043)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, Miscellaneous, DF-0602, 2006 (Box 95, Folder 1044)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, DF-0649, 2005-2008 (Box 95, Folder 1045)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, DF-0744, 2007-2009 (Box 95, Folder 1046)
  - Millennium Film Workshop, DF-0835, 2008-2009 (Box 95, Folder 1047)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum, B-01100, 2001-2003, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 1048)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum, Miscellaneous, B-01100, 2001-2003 (Box 95, Folder 1049)
  - Missouri Botanical Garden, EC-0320, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1050)
  - Mobius, B-0131, 2000-2002, 2007 (Box 96, Folder 1051)
  - Mobius, B-0322, 2000, 2003, 2006, 2009 (Box 96, Folder 1052)
  - Mobius, B-0322, Mobius_TMU, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 1052)
  - The Moebius Ensemble, B-0155, 2000-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1053)
  - Mongol-American Cultural Association, B-0132, 2000-2002, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 1054)
  - The Mongolia Society, EC-0204, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 96, Folder 1055)
  - Montalvo, B-0422, 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 96, Folder 1056)
  - Montalvo, Miscellaneous, B-0422, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 1057)
  - Montclair State University, B-0561, 2003, 2005-2007 (Box 96, Folder 1058)
  - Moscow Art Theatre School USA, EC-0613, 2005-2007 (Box 97, Folder 1059)
  - Moscow Art Theatre School USA, EC-0613, Studio VI, St. Petersburg, 2006 (Box 97, Folder 1059)
  - The Mostar Fund, Mostar 2004 Workshop Symposium, DF-0128, 2001-2002 (Box 97, Folder 1060)
  - The Mostar Fund, Lessons Learned, EC-0408, 2004-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 1061)
  - The Mostar Fund, Lessons Learned, EC-0408, Mostar, IVO Banac & Radio, 2004 July 22 (Box 97, Folder 1061)
  - The Mostar Fund, Lessons Learned, EC-0408, TMU Summary Report, Mostar 2004 Symposium "Lessons Learned", Report, Clippings, Photos, 2004 October 20 (Box 97, Folder 1061)
  - The Mostar Fund, DF-0513, 2005-2006 (Box 97, Folder 1062)
  - The Mostar Fund, B-0626, 2006, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 1064)
  - The Mountain Institute, B-0440, 2002-2006 (Box 97, Folder 1064)
  - Moving Theater of New York City, DF-0719, 2006-2008 (Box 97, Folder 1065)
  - Mum Puppettheatre, EC-0311, 1190-19914, 1996, 2001-2003 (Box 97, Folder 1066)
  - Mum Puppettheatre, EC-0311, Mum Puppettheatre, Poland, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 1066)
  - Mum Puppettheatre, Miscellaneous, EC-0311, 2001, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 1067)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, B-0364, 2003-2008 (Box 97, Folder 1068)
  - Museum of the History of Polish Jews, North American Council, B-0869, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 1069)
  - Museum of the History of Polish Jews, North American Council, Miscellaneous, B-0869, 2005-2006, 2009 (Box 97, Folder 1070)
  - The Museum of Jurassic Technology, B-0323, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1071)
  - The Museum of Jurassic Technology, B-0323, MJT/Kabinet Collaboration, Russia, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 1071)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), B-0133, 2001, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1072)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Visiting Scholar, Anda Rottenberg, EC-0106, 2001, 2004, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 1073)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), B-0291, 2002-2003 (Box 98, Folder 1074)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Russian Avant-Garde Book, DF-0207 (Canceled), 2002 (Box 98, Folder 1075)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Spring 2003 Symposium, DF-0305, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 1076)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Pushkin Exchange, B-0463, 2002-2007, 2009 (Box 98, Folder 1077)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Pushkin Exchange, Miscellaneous, B-0463, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 1078)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), DF-0404, 2003-2007 (Box 98, Folder 1079)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Curatorial Workshop and Olga Sviblova, DF-0438, 2004-2007 (Box 98, Folder 1080)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Seminar on Museum Sponsorship, Croatia, DF-0519, 2005-2006 (Box 98, Folder 1081)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Seminar on Museum Sponsorship, Croatia, DF-0519, Seminar on Museum Sponsorship, Zagreb, 2005 October 17-18 (Box 98, Folder 1081)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Infrared and Ramen Users Group (IRUG), and Reallocation of Lost Vanguard Symposium, DF-0537, 2005-2008 (Box 98, Folder 1082)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Infrared and Ramen Users Group (IRUG), DF-0537, IRUG Photos, Photographed by Patricia Romeu For the Museum of Modern Art, 2006 March 30-31 (Box 98, Folder 1082)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Infrared and Ramen Users Group (IRUG), and Reallocation of Lost Vanguard Symposium, Miscellaneous, DF-0537, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 1083)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Infrared and Ramen Users Group (IRUG), and Reallocation of Lost Vanguard Symposium, Miscellaneous, DF-0537, Vanguard Lost and Found, Symposium Audio (Box 98, Folder 1083)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), MoMA/State Russian Museum, B-0665, 2006-2009 (Box 98, Folder 1084)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), MoMA/State Russian Museum, B-0665, The Museum of Modern Art, Exchange with Pushkin Museum, Exchange with the State Russian Museum, Lost Vanguard: Soviet Modernist Architecture Symposium, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 1084)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), MoMA/Pushkin Exchange, B-0708, 2006-2009 (Box 98, Folder 1085)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Georgian Cinema, DF-0720, 2006-2010 (Box 98, Folder 1086)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), Pushkin Exchange, B-0827, 2008-2009 (Box 98, Folder 1087)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), B-0868, 2007-2010 (Box 98, Folder 1088)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), B-0868, The Museum of Modern Art, Interim Report to the Trust for Mutual Understanding, Sample Images, 2010 August 2 (Box 98, Folder 1088)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), B-0868, Images to Accompany MoMA 2009 Summer Travel Report (Box 98, Folder 1088)
  - The Mostar Fund, B-0290, 2002-2004, 2007-2009 (Box 99, Folder 1089)
  - Music for the Earth, EC-0321, 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 1090)
  - Music Mountain, DF-0501, 2004-2005 (Box 99, Folder 1091)
  - MusicaRussia Foundation, B-0180, 1996, 1998-2002, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 1092)
  - MusicaRussia Foundation, B-01113, 1999-2003, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 1093)
  - Nai-Ni Chen Dance Company, B-0424, 1993, 1995-1996, 1998, 2000-2001, 2003-2004, 2007-2008 (Box 99, Folder 1094)
  - Nai-Ni Chen Dance Company, B-0562, 1993, 1996, 1998, 2000-2001, 2003-2008 (Box 99, Folder 1095)
  - Nai-Ni Chen Dance Company, EC-0512, 1993, 1995-1996, 1998, 2000-2001, 2003-2008 (Box 99, Folder 1096)
  - Natasa Trifan Performance Group, DF-0702, 2006-2007 (Box 99, Folder 1097)
  - Natasa Trifan Performance Group, DF-0702, Natasa Trifan, Photos, Rehearsals, Shows (Box 99, Folder 1097)
  - National Audubon Society, B-0337, 2002-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 99, Folder 1098)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, B-0843, 2007-2010 (Box 99, Folder 1099)
  - National Gallery of Art, B-0464, 2004-2008 (Box 99, Folder 1100)
  - National Gallery of Art, Miscellaneous, B-0464, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 1101)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, B-01101, 2000-0004, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 1102)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, B-01101, Hermitage (Box 100, Folder 1102)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, EC-0517, 2005-2006 (Box 100, Folder 1103)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, EC-0709, 2006-2008 (Box 100, Folder 1104)
  - Native Forest Network, B-0435, 2003-2005 (Box 100, Folder 1105)
  - The Nature Conservancy, Mongolia, DF-0231, 2002-2004 (Box 100, Folder 1106)
  - The Nature Conservancy, B-0441, 2003-2006 (Box 100, Folder 1107)
  - The Nature Conservancy, B-0673, 2006-2008 (Box 101, Folder 1108)
  - The Nature Conservancy, B-0883, 2008-2009 (Box 101, Folder 1109)
  - The Nature Conservancy, Miscellaneous, B-0883, 2008 (Box 101, Folder 1110)
  - New Dance Alliance, DF-0745, 2000-2004, 2006-2008 (Box 101, Folder 1111)
  - New Dance Alliance, DF-0745, Fico Ballet Condi-Dance, Tiskarna Ljubljana, 2004 September (Box 101, Folder 1111)
  - New Dramatists, B-0365, 2003-2006 (Box 101, Folder 1112)
  - New England Music and Stage Company, DF-0746, 2006-2008 (Box 101, Folder 1113)